H.S. rewinds itself again, vanished years ago.
I have a question for you, though.
Are you there?
Coast, I want to show you something that I watched today.
This was, have you ever heard of like a relation?
Do I want to watch it?
Yeah, have you ever?
OK, do you want to watch either between,
do you want to watch either the cat in the squirrel
or the cat in the gorilla?
What's your choice?
Hang out and talk.
I know, but it's only a three-minute video. Do you want to watch the cat in the gorilla or the cat in the squirrel?
Can I choose neither?
No, you have to choose one of them
Did you choose the cat or the squirrel? Just say cat or just say gorilla or squirrel?
Okay, I'm playing the gorilla. I'm playing the gorilla.
You're forcing me into a fucking outro.
because it's the most amazing thing you've ever seen in your life.
You've never seen something like this.
This is incredible.
Watch this.
This is what it looks like.
I don't want to see it.
I'm here to watch this.
You have to see this.
Look.
I don't want to see LES or Sam on it.
I'm not pretty sure.
You know, we're supposed to get more people here,
but by playing this video,
you're not going to get more people on it.
You're not going to get more people on this video.
What is the point in playing that?
That's good.
Come on, dawg.
How do you play in this, dawg?
I'm fucking streaming right now.
Come on, dawg.
Follow me, brother.
Yeah, it goes to you.
Thank you.
Now, I'll explain to you, ghost.
What I had was, I had, like, a people joining interested,
but then they saw this, they saw that, and they were,
they were watching it, and then they heard your whiny, bitchy voice
over it, and they're like, oh, and it was, the moment was ruined.
So you ruined the moment.
That's a beautiful video. I mean, it's like, I mean, how can it not be beautiful without you trying to ruin?
I mean, it's like what I mean, what?
But it was nice. I mean, it's like, but now I can you embarrass me have me come up on
This day to try and tell me what to do boss me around about it
Being so rude. Can't even like watch like a three-minute video
Understand so in the final time and I'm not I'm gonna talk to you for